[{"answer": "That I know", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "My body is frightened, but I am not", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, sir, I wouldn't say that. As a matter of fact, he was quite eloquent", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " What is it? What's happened", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh, so you've had a vision again", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What an imagination you have", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Perhaps it was the kind of reality you told us about when you saw the Devil painting our wagon wheels red, using his tail as a brush", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "To make one of the balls stand absolutely still in the air", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Impossible for us", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What is it", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Sit still. Don't move", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Don't say anything", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I thought it would serve to remind people that they must die", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Why should one always make people happy? It might not be a bad idea to scare them a little once in a while", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "If you do scare them ..", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And if they think ..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Through my indifference to my fellow men, I have isolated myself from their company. Now I live in a world of phantoms. I am imprisoned in my dreams and fantasies", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yes, I do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What are you waiting for", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You want guarantees", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "But He remains silent", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Perhaps no one is there", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "That's possible", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No, I haven't. But if I had seen her and she looked like you, I'd quickly forget that I'd seen her", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Have you seen my wife", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well, in that case you haven't seen her", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's nice. But it's surely too expensive for me", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Has she disappeared", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, he'll soon be two", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Do you do tricks also", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Is my friend going to be an acrobat", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "We certainly do. And my friend is a very skillful juggler", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend wants him to be", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend wants him to be", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I don't know.  Perhaps he'll become a knight", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It might be wise to have company going through the forest. It's said to be full of trolls and ghosts and bandits. That's what I've heard", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " After all, I have become director of the whole company", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " What's your name", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "How old are you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Why have you crushed her hands", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Who did", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I'm sawing down your tree because your time is up", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "So you haven't got time", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Then it's canceled because of death", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Your contract is terminated", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "We feel that something is going to happen to us, but we don't know what", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "The day of judgment ..", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yes, what is it", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "What do you see", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "The knight is sitting over there playing chess", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "But do you see who he's playing with", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "But do you see who he's playing with", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "No, no, he isn't alone", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "He is alone. You mustn't frighten me this way", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Who is it, then", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "You seem anxious. Are you hiding anything", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Nothing escapes me. No one escapes from me", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "That's true", "docId": "seventhseal.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Yes, I did", "qsentId": 62}]